{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "Which event handler will run when a user is finished filling out a form?",
      "answers": [
        "onSubmit",
        "onClick",
        "onChange",
        "onForm"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Define JSX",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "answer1": "J",
      "answer2": "J",
      "answer3": "S",
      "answer4": "S",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "what is JSX",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "answer1": "JavaScript XML",
      "answer2": "javascript",
      "answer3": "htm",
      "answer4": "Java",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ddd",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "answer1": "ddd",
      "answer2": "ddc",
      "answer3": "ccc",
      "answer4": "fff",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "hhhhh",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "answer1": "llll",
      "answer2": "kkk",
      "answer3": "hhh",
      "answer4": "ggg",
      "id": 11
    }
  ]
}